You know her?
She's one of the girls I killed.
Teddy: Whoever's looking for her.
we need to figure out who that is.
Oh. I'm Victoria. by the way.
Reed Thompson.
Alejandro: You'll be ready
to purchase another 25 keys?
[Beep. line ringing] Lucia: No problem.
We'll be in contact.
Since when do we care
what Gustavo wants?
I made him a partner.
[Moaning]
Papa? I've got to tell you something.
Niggas broke into my spot. tie me up.
and hit me with a
motherfucking baseball bat.
[Groans]
Swim: You see that? You see those rocks?
- It's my new favorite.
- I ain't never seen that before.
- Fuck is that?
- Our future.
[Funk music playing]
♪♪
Y'all cutting that shit too small. man.
♪ Keep going. keep going ♪
♪ A-keep going ♪
♪ Don't you give up. keep going ♪
♪ Keep going. keep going ♪
Man. we've been at this
shit for like a hour.
Can't we get some bitches to do this?
Already did.
Nigga got jokes.
We should be out there
hustling right now.
No. no. no.
We're not selling this batch.
We gonna give it away.
What? For free?
Motherfucker. you done lost your mind?
Man. how we supposed to get paid. man?
Avi called this shit garbage.
Threw it in my face. Why?
Because he don't know what it is.
Nobody in L.A. knows
what it is. not yet.
Ain't a market for it.
So... we gonna create it.
This motherfucker talking about markets
like he Dow Jones.
Y'all weren't there. This
ain't no regular high.
One taste from this shit.
motherfuckers be feenin'.
And when they do. you tell
them to bring their cash
to MLK Park tomorrow. all right?
So. uh...
you're gonna let us sample
the product this time. right?
I mean. this ain't coke. We
gotta gain a little knowledge
if we're gonna educate the masses.
Just tell 'em it's good.
Yeah. but I wanna know how good.
♪ Then I know you can move your feet ♪
- Fine.
- Really?
On you.
But develop a taste for that shit.
and you can go back to moving
furniture to make your ends.
Man. my couch humping days
are over. Don't worry 'bout me.
What you think? This will work?
I don't know.
One small step for man. right?
♪ Get up. get up. get
up. get up. get up ♪
♪ Right up on. we're gonna funk you ♪
- ♪ Right on up. funk you ♪
- [Flame sizzles]
♪ Right up. we're gonna funk you ♪
♪ Right on up ♪
♪ Get up. get up. get
up. get up. get up ♪
[Exhales deeply]
♪ Get up. get up. get up ♪
♪ Sit back down ♪
♪ Right on up. we're gonna funk you ♪
- ♪ Right on up. funk ♪
- Oh... Fuck
Let's see that shit.
[Gasps] Fuck.
[Coughs]
Shit.
Holy fuck.
Oh. man.
♪ Yoda-lay-hee-hoo ♪
Oh. fuck.
Yo. I'm good. [Clatter]
♪ I said get up. get up.
get up. get up. get up ♪
[Laughs. coughs]
♪ Get up. get up. get
up. get up. get up ♪
We gonna make bank.
♪ Sit back down ♪
- Synced and corrected by javiernv -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[Pouring]
- Man: [Shouts] Order up!
- Woman: Thank you.
[Bell dings]
[Sighs]
Relax. Mm.
Everybody in L.A.'s at least
10 minutes late for everything.
- Thank you for coming with me.
- Seriously?
Finding Kristin could mean finding Jess.
Right.
[Door bell jingles. door opens]
[Door closes]
[Sighs]
You got some way of contacting him or...
Just his name.
Mm. Jim Stewart.
Wait. what? Ooh...
Sorry. it's just... Jimmy Stewart?
[Door bell jingles. door closes]
Oh. my God.
Wait. do you think it's a scam?
I don't know. I mean.
could be a coincidence.
[Groans] Sh...
- Hey...
- Man: 24. order up.
[Sighs]
[Imitates Jimmy Stewart]:
"The money is in youse house
Right next to yours.
And the Kennedys' house.
and Mrs. Macklin's house. too.
- and a hundred others."
- "And a hundred others."
[Both chuckle]
I'm sorry. Oh...
I love Jimmy Stewart. Are you a fan?
Oh. no. at heart. I'm more
of a Cary Grant girl. so...
Hmm.
[Man speaks indistinctly]
[Sighs] Oh. gosh.
Do you wanna keep waiting
or should we get out of here?
Fuck it. Let's just... Let's go. okay?
[Door bell jingles]
Oh. God.
[British accent] Hello? [Door closes]
- Ah. I can see the resemblance.
- Are you Jim Stewart?
Yeah. Yeah. it's in
the nose. in the eyes.
Faces worth remembering.
Wait. um. so you really knew Kristin?
Well. don't know if I'd go that far.
We partied one night.
There was an Asian chick there as well.
She had fake bits. Brilliant.
- So where was this?
- Some club.
Don't quite remember the name. [Sighs]
I might be able to remember better
if my tourist visa wasn't expiring.
Wait. what?
Money to hire a lawyer.
That would almost
certainly jog my memory.
I reckon a few thousand
should do it. [Sighs]
[Sips]
She had a dimple on her chin.
and she did a mean Bonnie Tyler.
just in case you think I'm not for real.
Wait. But...
I mean. I don't have
a few thousand dollars.
I do.
I got more in the car. I
keep it there for emergencies.
Come on.
[Door bell jingles]
Now. you're doing me a
real favor here. mate.
If I just get this visa sorted. then...
- Sure. It's in the trunk. So...
- ...then I can gig again.
It's a... it's... it's a punk rock thing.
Now I'm right at a vanguard
of this... Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
You are a special kind of
piece of shit. aren't you?
[Bone snapping]
- Fuck!
- Tell me the name of the club right now
or I'm gonna break
your fucking arm. Jimmy.
- [Bone snapping]
- All right. all right!
It's the Glitter Club.
[Groans] Fuck.
[Whispers] Wow.
[Birds chirping]
Gustavo. Nice boots.
I see we're taking
good care of you. hmm?
I bought them for him.
His old ones had holes in them.
Yeah. well. Lucia.
Siempre tan linda. huh?
[Sniffs]
Your father is in the study.
He's been askin' for ya.
Okay.
Don't take too long.
He needs his strength.
I haven't seen you in a couple of days.
Yeah.
I've been busy.
Ahorita vengo.
[Door closes]
[Knock on door]
[Knocks]
[Chain clacks]
Hey.
[Exhales]
I've been calling you.
What's wrong?
The camp was hit.
When?
- Early this morning.
- Elena?
- I don't know yet.
- The coke?
You think I give a shit about
the fucking coke right now?
Right. sorry. I...
I'll. um. I'll ask around.
I'll see what intel I can scrounge up.
No. no. I'm going down there. Teddy.
Right now. We both should.
[Sighs]
What?
Does Club Glitter mean anything to you?
[Breathes sharply]
- [Exhales]
- All right. look. don't worry.
Just... you go. I'll stay here.
I'll make sure she doesn't
get any further than that.
[Breathes sharply]
I thought approaching
her was a bad idea. but...
you were right.
Look. if you're gonna go
down there. be careful.
The whole area's probably still hot.
And the last thing I need iis
you getting yourself killed.
I will.
Thanks. Teddy.
[Breathes sharply]
♪♪
♪ So 1. 2. 3 ♪
Kevin: It's like that. uh.
"Prince and the Pauper" nigga.
Them old motherfuckers from
back in the day. man. you know?
But except ain't no price.
It's just a rich white boy
from Wall Street. right?
And he get tricked to
switch places with Eddie
by these other crusty old
rich white guys. right?
And Eddie becomes a
Wall Street dude. man.
And the Wall Street dude.
he turn poor and shit
and they start treating
whitey like he a nigga.
Shit crazy. man.
And then. Eddie on the
floor pretending like
he ain't got no legs and
the police come over. man.
And they start. "hey man.
what are you doing?"
- And he's like...
- Nigga. I was with you. all right?
We saw that shit. like.
two weeks ago with Franklin.
Really? Are you sure?
Oh. yeah.
Hear y'all giving away some new high.
He got you.
Hey. hold up. Hold up. hold up. hold up.
Spread the word. all right?
Tell everybody.
Hey. man. um. how many of these
we give away? Like... like 30?
- Nah. more like 10.
- Really?
Ain't given away 30 rocks. nigga.
You sure?
Really?
Hey. wh-what you all giving. man?
Something new and improved.
- Shit. hit me with a couple.
- Nah. nigga. you getting one.
[Chuckles] Let me have two. man.
Hey cuz I said you
getting one. all right?
Now you can come back
tomorrow and pay $10.
[Scoffs] All right.
[Spits] Hey. hook this nigga up.
All right. come here.
- Who's that?
- What's up?
We got that new high.
He gonna hook y'all up when he done.
Hey! Hey. man. Hey. Leon! Leon!
Come on! Come on! Calm down. bitch!
- Hey! Hey. Leon!
- The fuck off me!
[Shouting indistinctly]
- Get the fuck off my homie!
- Whoo!
Hey. kick his ass!
Get... hey. man. these my new Adidas!
- Hey. let go of my leg. man!
- Hey. what the fuck you doing?
- Get him off me. Leon!
- Get the fuck off his leg.
Man. these my new Adidas.
cuz! Get off me. man!
♪♪
[Sizzling]
[Inhales deeply]
[Exhales]
We have to talk.
About what's gonna
happen with the business.
Always so impatient.
Ever since you were little.
I remember one time your
mom was doing cemitas.
You wanted one. but she said no.
That evening. she was doing the wash.
And she sees you coming
out of the kitchen
wearing these old. dirty overalls.
[Laughs]
I've never worn overalls.
[Laughs] Mm. She stripped you
right there in the hallway
Two cemitas come tumbling out.
[Both laugh]
Oh... the reason I remember is
You said that extra cemita
was for your sister.
I know it's hard to let someone in
after what happened to this family.
Mija.
you're smart. innovative. fierce.
But you can't do it alone.
You need people that you can count on.
That's what helps you prosper
That's what makes a life.
[Crying]
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
["Words to My Song"
by Dry Bread playing]
[Indistinct conversations]
♪♪
Uh. you take the bar.
I'll take the floor.
Okay.
♪ Someone took the words to my song ♪
♪ The next time I write a song ♪
♪ There ain't gonna be no words ♪
♪ Let the music go on ♪
♪ Oh. yes. I will ♪
♪♪
[Sighs]
♪ Oh. yes. I will ♪
Hey. Hi.
Any luck?
No. you?
No.
[Women chattering]
Fuck.
You know. I really thought there
would be something here. right?
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Come on. you wanna get out of here?
[Chattering. laughing]
[Sighs]
[Funk music playing]
[Man exhales]
No.
Let's get shitfaced and dance.
♪♪
- Yeah. I don't dance.
- Come on.
I seem to remember Stewart getting down
in "It's a Wonderful Life."
Or does your impression
just end at the voice?
Bartender. uh. we'll
have a shot over here.
What do you want? Um.
anything but tequila.
Oh. I'd love a shot
of tequila. please.
Man: Coming up.
[Glasses clink]
Oh!
- Another round.
- You got it.
♪♪
Price point's right.
We don't have to sell to
white folks or Mexicans.
We sell it right here.
and. uh. same as weed.
But for big paper.
That takes care of your
problems with yeyo. right?
How big?
You would know big.
Off a single key. the way we cut it.
we make 50... Selling nickels.
But it catches on and we set
the market. we sell dimes.
- $100.000 off a single key?
- A-ha
And people be coming back.
Try if you want.
Oh. fuck that.
Nah. I've been fools into
freebase. That shit is nasty.
All I know is. this will catch on.
And when it does.
we could be makin'
seven figures a month.
All right. We'll give your
little shit away for right now
- and we can see how it go.
- [Claps hands]
[Laughs] Thanks. Unc.
- See you. Aunt Lou.
- Bye.
Hey. if it do pop off the
way that you're thinkin'.
it's gonna make some noise.
You thought about what you
gonna tell yout mama?
I'm thinking on that.
Keep thinkin'.
[Doors creak]
[Lock clicks]
Franklin gon' do this
with or without us.
Be better for him if we in on it.
What? You trying to protect
the boy? [Bag rustles]
We got a good life here. don't we?
[Rustling] Damn.
Yeah.
But still ain't enough. right?
When I was a little girl in Baton Rouge.
we ain't had no TV. but
we had this big 'ol radio
with a record player on top.
And that mug would transmit
all the way from Chicago.
WLS. [Laughs]
And on Sunday nights. they
would play live big band.
And I would imagine the
women in their evening dresses
and the men in their tuxedos.
And. baby. I wanted more than
anything to be in that room.
You sound like a little girl right now.
Maybe I do. [Clatter]
But seven figures a month. baby.
this world will be whatever
the fuck we want it.
♪♪
[Laughs] Yes! Mm!
Yes! Mm!
Yes! [Laughing]
- [Horse whinnies. blusters]
- No. no. no. no. no.
Quieto. quieto. quieto. quieto. Hey.
What are you doing out
here skulking like a thief?
Just took a walk.
Mira. Pedro. Take him.
I'll catch up with you. okay?
[Horse whinnies. blusters]
If I had known you'd been
around. I would've invited you.
You ever been riding at night?
I've never been riding. señor.
- Never?
- Never.
What kind of a Mexican are you?
[Both laugh]
Your father never took you?
Nunca. señor.
[Horse blusters]
Hey. papa. dale. dale.
He still around. your father?
No. señor.
¿Y tú mamá?
Dios los tenga en su gloria.
What happened?
Killed.
When I was young.
Sorry to hear.
¿Y hermanos. y primos y todo eso?
[Horse blusters] [Whistles softly]
There is nobody. señor.
No más. yo.
Qué pena.
Well. at least you still have us. huh?
I do think you need some riding lessons.
[Both chuckle]
Hijo de la chingada
[Horse blustering]
♪ Ooh! Is ya funkin'.
baby. is ya funkin' ♪
♪ Aye. is ya funkin'. baby. is ya ♪
♪♪
♪ Baby. is ya funkin' ♪
♪ Baby. is ya funkin' tonight ♪
Hey. Hey!
- I can help you.
- Good. Thank you.
I can help you.
♪ Tonight ♪
No. I...
- You're looking for Kristin. right?
- What?
- You're looking for Kristin?
- Yeah.
- Let's go talk. Let's go talk.
- Okay.
♪ Move it all over ♪
♪ I want to funk you all night. girl ♪
♪ Stroke it down. do it with feeling ♪
Of course she was here. I
was the one who invited her.
See. we had just started
doubling up in class
- and she was my partner. and this was
- Wait. Class? What class?
Uh. you know. aerial
dance. the art of trapeze.
No. I was wondering if...
Wait. so were you guys
hanging out that night. or...
Yeah. Well. well. I was working.
but she was partying. though.
She had to blow off some steam.
you know. because of Nate.
That fucking asshole. I told her that...
So what happened then?
Did she leave alone?
Um. no. but she met some
guys and left with them.
Guys... What guys?
I don't know. One kind
of had like a faint
frat-holey thing going on.
The other one was really hot.
Kinda looked like a heavier
Latino Freddie Mercury.
Okay. so who were they. though?
Do you know their names or anything?
No. just that they were
going to keep partying
at the frat-hole's place.
And they asked me to go
- and I was going to. but then I pulled
- So where were they headed?
- What was the address?
- Um. I... you know what?
I may have written it down
That's possible. Coming through.
Let's see...
This is a disaster.
What does that say?
Oh. no. no. no. no. [Papers shuffling]
No. I don't know.
♪♪
Oh my God. That guy's such a creep.
I'm so sorry. I like.
never write anything...
Oh. my God. Wait. no. no. no.
[Gasps] Fuck me sideways
with a tire iron. That's it.
- That's it?
- Yeah. that... that's it!
Oh. thank you! Wow! [Laughing]
- Oh. my God!
- Okay...
I never write shit down.
Can I take this? That's in...
This has never happened to me before.
- Thank you. Yeah. wow.
- I hope you find Kristin.
Yeah. She's like... she had
the best straddle whip in class.
- Thank you.
- And she always brought me Skittles.
- Yeah. thank you.
- And I thought that was so sweet.
- Thank you so much.
- Bye. guys. Bye!
You know what? I gotta use the restroom.
Just two minutes. I'll meet
you by the front door.
Okay.
Don't take too long. Uh...
♪ Come back alone ♪
♪♪
Hey. it's McDonald. Uh.
listen. I need you...
♪♪
[Camera shutter clicks]
[Lowered voice] I don't
know. As long as it takes.
Please just do it.
Thank you.
[Coins drop]
♪ He had the groove ♪
♪ Had the groove ♪
- ♪ That makes you move ♪
- Excuse me.
Can I have these drinks? Thanks.
♪ That makes you wanna get
down. down. down. down ♪
♪♪
[Sighs]
[Mutters indistinctly]
[Gasping]
♪♪
♪ Disco beat ♪
[Coughing] [Ashtray clatters]
[Retching]
[Grunting]
[Vomits] [Crowd gasps]
Ah! What the fuck. man?
[Shouting indistinctly]
- Back off!
- Shit!
[Shouting continues]
- Okay. okay!
Are you okay?
[Song ends]
[Insects chirping]
Tio.
This used to be the setting porch
You used to love to play here.
Your father moved out all
the furniture... [Snip]
...turned it into this.
It makes him happy.
It gives him peace.
You make him happy.
¿Verdad? ¿Y tú. feliz?
Claro que sí.
Uh-huh. You should talk. then...
about how you see everything moving
forward in this business.
I'm not sure I understand what you mean.
Well. you know. you're
bright. ambitious.
I'm sure you have ideas. [Snip]
You know. changes that
you might want to make.
How you see things into the future.
[Snip]
Pedro told you. didn't he?
Of course he told me. [Snip]
[Door closes]
[Footsteps approach]
¿Qué onda?
I think you should stop
sleeping in the stash house.
You have some money now.
Get out of that shithole
and go find your own place.
- Okay.
- Teddy: I got it. I got it.
- [Victoria sighs]
[Lock clicks]
- So it's just there. um...
- Shit.
- ...there on the right.
- Oh. shit. oh. shit. oh. shit. shit.
If you... would you grab
me that medical kit.
Yeah. I got it. okay.
- It's just under the seat.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah. okay.
[Keys jangle]
[Breathing heavily]
[Toilet flushes]
[Breathes sharply]
[Oven door creaks]
[Whispers] Okay.
Here you go. Oh. thanks.
Oh. God. Oh. fuck. I need some water.
Uh...
[Groans. exhales] [Water running]
[Thud]
[Groans]
[Exhales]
That's your nephew?
Um...
no. actually.
- Oh. you're married?
- Separated.
How long?
I'm sorry. do you mind if we don't...
Yeah. no. sorry. Of course.
I shouldn't have asked. Just...
[Sighs]
Okay. [Inhales sharply]
Are you gonna be all right?
Yeah. I think I'll live.
Okay.
Hey. thank you so much for everything.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna head out.
- Wait. where are you goin'?
- What do you mean?
I just. uh. We both had a lot to drink.
And. um. it's probably just
safer for you to crash here.
- I'll sleep on the couch.
- No. I'm gonna go to that house. Reed.
It's like 1 in the morning.
I don't give a fuck
what time it is. okay?
She said that they host late
night parties. [Unlocks door]
All right. all right. all right. just...
I'm gonna go change real fast. And...
No. I really think that you should rest.
Hey. we're in this together. Right?
Okay.
Hurry up.
You know he crazy. right? [Laughing]
[Alarm honking in distance] [Chattering]
[Basketball hits backboard. dribbling]
[Hip-hop music playing faintly]
♪♪
- What's up with it?
- How's shit goin'?
Told you. nigga.
- Fat-ass hobo pulled a knife on me.
- Oh. shit.
Got his blood all
over my fucking kicks. man.
Damn.
- You good. though?
- Yeah. he ain't stick me.
But you're gonna reimburse
me for these shoes. though.
[Laughs] Yeah. sure.
Give you 50 cents. you can
walk your ass down to Goodwill.
Man. fuck you.
Your mama dress you up your whole life.
- but I gotta pay for my own shit.
- Hold up. Are you real?
Real as death. nigga.
And I want a little extra
to pay for my frayed nerves.
Hazard pay.
It's fair. Saint. I mean.
we are putting our lives on
the line for this thing. man.
You wanna talk about lives on the line?
I almost died twice
since I started this shit.
Man. this nigga full of excuses.
but you ain't nothing but
a cheap ass motherfucker.
[Laughs] You get poked one
time on some junkie ass blade.
What about me? I've been
robbed. beat. shot at.
You wanna talk about hazard pay.
where's my hazard pay. motherfucker?
You know what? Fine.
You want money? Here. take some money.
Man. who done all the
fucking killing for you. man?
- Step the fuck back.
- But now you're some king or some shit?
You gonna tell me how to
wipe my own fucking ass?
- I said step the fuck back!
- Hey.
[Sighs]
- Fuck...
- Hey. man. Hey. what the...
Hey. man. What are y'all doing. man?
Hey. hey! Come on. man. [Grunting]
Give me what you owe me.
you square ass Mama boy!
Get the fuck off me. you
jailbird motherfucker!
- Hey. hey. hey...
- Fuck you. bougie-ass motherfucker!
- Hey. fuck you...
- Hey. be cool. man!
Cool out. man!
Hey! Cool out. man!
Y'all acting like some bitches. Fuck!
We're sitting on a
silent fucking gold mine
- if y'all don't fuck it up!
- Man. fuck you! And fuck all this shit.
Man. I don't have to be
babysitting y'all. man.
Leon Sim is the man with
the fucking plans. huh?
Ah. fuck you!
[Groans]
Come on. Le! Le! Leon!
[Dog continues barking]
Teddy: Quiet neighborhood.
[Car door closes]
[Breathing heavily]
Victoria: Just do...
Dang it. [Dials call box. beep]
Hello? Is anyone there?
[Call box squawks]
- Hello?!
- Whoa. whoa. hey.
What?
Great. [Grunts]
Now we're trespassing.
It's okay. Well. then. don't come.
Oh. no. no. getting shot would
be the perfect end to this day.
- Hope they don't have a dog.
- [Lights click on]
Excuse me?
What do you think you're doing?
Oh. sorry. Hey. this is your house?
Yes. and it's private property.
I'm sorry. Uh. all right. this is...
I'm looking for someone... My sister.
She went missing a couple of
weeks ago and somebody told me
that she went to a party at this house
the last night that anyone saw her.
A party here?
The only kind of parties we
throw come with birthday hats
and kids under 9.
I have a photograph.
Do you... Do you recognize her?
No. And as sorry as I am
to hear about your sister.
I want you to leave. or
I'm calling the police.
Yeah. okay. Hey...
Of course.
Sorry for bothering you.
So. look. if you remember anything else.
my name's Reed Thompson.
- It's in the book.
- Of course. Mr. Thompson.
[Whispers] The rope is a nice touch.
[Normal voice] Thank you for your help.
[Crying]
[Exhales] I miss her so much.
[Exhales]
Trapeze class? I mean.
what was she gonna do?
Run off and join Barnum & Bailey?
[Sniffles]
I don't know. I guess I
just didn't know her anymore.
[Crying]
[Sobbing]
- [Humming]
- You all right?
Mnh-mnh.
Uh. nah. man.
Our world ain't on fire anymore. huh?
I feel like this tiny animal
gnawing in my brain. man.
Yeah. probably best to leave
that out the sales pitch.
Yeah. you right.
Heard from Leon?
No.
Don't worry he'll come around.
Man. come on. He always do.
Like that time you bought
the same exact shirt as him.
He always come back and eat pie
at the end of the day. right?
- [Speaking indistinctly]
- Franklin: Eat pie?
You know. like. eat pie.
Humble pie. Humble.
[Cheering]
Oh. you wouldn't know
nothin' about that.
[Laughs]
[Basketball dribbling.
shouting continues]
You think they here for us?
[Chuckles] Yes. they are.
Breakfast time. ladies and gentlemen.
Who's first?
Cuidado que no se les tire.
Señoras pongan atención.
You fucking piece of shit!
[Object thuds]
You have the balls to come in
here after running to Daddy?
Look at this place.
You two have really
put your work in. huh?
I'm not sure that this is how
I would've done it. but. uh...
Looks good.
Anyone else here?
Gustavo?
I don't know where he is.
You tell him about our discussion?
'Cause if I find out
you lied to me again...
He doesn't know anything.
Good.
Let's go here and. uh. have a talk.
[Keys jingling]
[Knocking]
Hey. Saint. You home?
Hey. my nigga. My bad
about yesterday. all right?
Open up if you in there. Come on.
[Knocking] Come on. Saint.
[Clicking]
Let's squash all this.
[Pounding on door] Come on. man.
[Scoffs]
[Speaks indistinctly] ...was fun.
but this business. all right?
Mnh-mnh. That ain't cool.
You know I good for it.
It's 10 or nothing. sweetheart.
I don't make the rule.
Get you free Frosties for life.
Frosties?
Do you think I got this body
tossing back milkshakes. huh?
Finish what you got. man.
I'm-a head back to the
crib and restock. all right?
- All right. I got you.
- Back in 20.
- Cool.
- Baby. you ain't listenin'.
I done my shift. I pay you double.
Walk away. Mama.
This ain't no credit union. bitch.
[Scoffs]
Or I tell your mama. What's up. man?
Thank you. thank you.
♪♪
[Doors creak]
[Beads clack]
[Sighs]
[Turns off faucet]
[Glass clatters]
[Groaning]
Leon.
Leon!
[Breathing heavily]
Motherfucker caught me slippin'. man.
[Grunts]
[Breathing raggedly]
I'm... I'm calling an
ambulance. all right?
Wait. Wait. [Gasping]
[Door opens and closes]
Hello? I need an ambulance.
My friend's been shot.
- 1127 West 56th.
- [Gasping]
I called them. They on they way.
It's gonna be all right.
- [Whispers] The crack.
- Hey.
- The crack.
- What?
The crack. the crack.
The crack. The crack.
Fuck. fuck! Fuck!
[Beads clacking]
I'm coming! Aah!
Fuck!
Aah!
[Beads clacking]
- [Breathing heavily]
- I'm coming. man!
I'm coming out!
[Panting] I got it.
[Gasping]
Shh. shh. Hold on. Hold
on. They on they way.
They on they way. man. huh?
You're not gonna die.
You're not gonna die. Shh.
Okay? [Siren wailing in distance]
- Fuck.
- You're not gonna die.
[Gasping]
[Sirens wailing]
[Siren whoops. brakes squeal]
[Car door opens and
closes. radio chatter]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org